https://www.jihadwatch.org/privacy

Why Jihad Watch?
Jan 11th 2019
At jihadwatch.org (www.jihadwatch.org), the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.
This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
1. Log Files
We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:
Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
Types of browser
Internet Service Provider (ISP)
Date and time stamp
Pages visited and the method used
Referring and exit pages
Number of clicks
All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.
We will use this logged data to combat malicious abuse and to improve usability for our visitors, and for no other purpose.
Encrypted log files are stored with a cloud hosting provider (off site) for a period of 6 weeks, at which time they are deleted and the storage space overwritten.
2. Cookies
We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, we have no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites. You may access Our Site without providing any data at all, and the use of a VPN for privacy and security is encouraged.
3. Legal disclosure
In certain circumstances We may be legally required to share certain data held by Us, which may include your personal information, for example, where We are involved in legal proceedings, where We are complying with the requirements of legislation, a court order, or a governmental authority. We do not require any further consent from you in order to share your data in such circumstances and will comply as required with any legally binding request that is made of Us.
4. Other
Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communications from jihadwatch.org. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.
If you subscribe to follow up comments, or have email notifications of all post (10+ emails a day) WordPress’s commercial arm automattic.com have access to your name and email address for that purpose.
If you subscribe to the daily digest (a single daily email) mailchimp.com mailerlite.com manage that so would have access to your name and email address.
Both automattic.com and mailchimp.com mailerlite.com have proven to be apolitical, and not known to be cavalier with users data, both having their reputations intact. Both have their own privacy notices publicly available.
We do at times enforce Javascript to view the site, this script poses no risk to the browser, and is purely used to mitigate DDoS attacks.
You have the legal right to ask for a copy of any of your personal data held by Us (where such data is held). If the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive we may charge a “reasonable fee” for the administrative costs of complying with the request.
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at marc@jihadwatch.org.
Share this:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on WhatsApp (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)Click to email this to a friend (Opens in new window)MoreClick to share on Skype (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Telegram (Opens in new window)Click to share on Tumblr (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pocket (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window) FacebookYoutubeTwitterLog in
Subscribe to the Jihad Watch Daily Digest
You will receive a daily mailing containing links to the stories posted at Jihad Watch in the last 24 hours.
Enter your email address to subscribe.
Email
Name
Please wait...
Thank you for signing up!
If you are forwarding to a friend, please remove the unsubscribe buttons first, as they my accidentally click it.
Subscribe to all Jihad Watch posts
You will receive immediate notification.
Enter your email address to subscribe.
Note: This may be up to 15 emails a day.
Email Address
Subscribe
Search Site
Translate
The Team
Robert Spencer in FrontPageMag
Robert Spencer in PJ Media
Articles at Jihad Watch by
Archives
2020DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2019DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2018DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2017DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2016DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2015DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2014DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2013DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2012DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2011DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2010DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2009DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2008DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2007DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2006DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2005DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2004DecemberNovemberOctoberSeptemberAugustJulyJuneMayAprilMarchFebruaryJanuary2003DecemberNovemberOctoberMarch
All Categories
All Categories
Select Category
“Islamophobia”
“Tiny Minority of Extremists”
Abu Dhabi
academia
Afghanistan
Ahmadis
air security
Al-Qaeda
Al-Shabaab
Alawites
Islamic Society of North America
Islamic State (aka ISIS, ISIL, Daesh)
Islamic supremacism
Islamicize Me
Israel
Italy
Ivory Coast
Jamaica
Japan
Jerusalem
jihad charities
Jihad doctrine
Jihad in prisons
Jihad in the U.S.
Jihad in the West
Jihad Watch Awards
Jihadist intimidation and thuggery
Jordan
journalistic bias
Kashmir
Kazakhstan
Kenya
Recent Comments
Lavéritétriomphera on Macron: ‘France has no problem with Islam’Cicero on Happy Hanukkah!newsupplements on Macron: ‘France has no problem with Islam’newsupplements on Macron: ‘France has no problem with Islam’Lavéritétriomphera on Macron: ‘France has no problem with Islam’
Popular Categories
dhimmitude
Sharia
Jihad in the U.S
ISIS / Islamic State / ISIL
Iran
Free Speech
Robert Spencer FaceBook Page
